[{"answer": "I've had big arguments on that and friends of Obama said they're not lying.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "Did he mislead or was it just a blatant lie?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "In my book--", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "But that wasn't lie, isn't it?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yeah, let me say a couple of things.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "How damaging is all these to him, personally in terms of his credibility?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, I believe in due course the head will roll.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "And she is the obvious head?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "This is doable idea.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Do you think the fundamentally ObamaCare is a good idea, now a problem has been the implementation or you think the whole thing is basically flawed?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "I must say I was speechless at that one.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "How bad is that?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "ERGEN: Yes, but, let me just say, I think that whether this program is going to work or not is highly problematic right now.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Can Presidents comeback in the second term when the clock is ticking from such a major fiasco?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, that should worry you.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "What will?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "\"THE STORY\": Well, I think it's very damaging.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "And how successfully can the President extricate himself from this mess?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Well, you're right.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "That's got to be pretty bad, isn't it?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "ARANISS: Well, first of all, you're assuming that Hillary Clinton will run and she'll be the candidate, and at this point, before 2008, nobody even knew about Barack Obama.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "How does that impact on Hillary Clinton if at all?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "Well, I think he said that he made a mistake.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Do you feel any sense of disappointment in the way this has gone?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "But Robert Redford, was interesting about is, he came out and said that Obama's paralyzing the system, behaving stupidly.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "What's wrong with the country?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Yeah, I do.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "EINSTEIN: I guess there was but it was much more focused in getting Ridge (ph) good laugh and, you know, Clinton could laugh back and, you know, they joke back and forth.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "And then more so, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "At the White House.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "At the White House last week?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Do you think that if, it was George W. Bush who made the mistake, you know, that Obama would be beating on him everyday?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I think, you know, you mean running for an election, you whack him.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "When enemies are vulnerable, you whack him, don't you?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "I think, you know, they were excited.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "What was a mood like in the White House when you were there?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "I love him, you know, and I think the guy is fantastic and, you know, I had a conversation with him and he said, \"Wait till I win, you know, my gubernatorial race.\"", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Can you enjoy the work of someone like Chris Christie even though he's on the other side?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Anything that Mrs. Clinton asks me to do, you know, I will do because I think she represents the best path for 2016.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Will you stumping to Hillary if she runs?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Well, one thing it was great for us to see was what it really looked like is Harvey and I were running around doing 50 other things and the cameras were capturing everything else.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "What was it like to be behind the scenes with all this legends?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Robinhood eats all the overhead unlike some of the charities that we all give money to, where you find out that the charity director made a million dollars and his cousin got $400,000 and they paid for the dry cleaning, all the money.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "But in terms of money Harvey, huge amounts have been raised, more will be raised obviously from the movie as well, how is it best being used to the moment?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Maybe 192 Oscars.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "How many have you won now?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Well, you know, at the Weinstein Company we give breaks to young, you know, talent and we decided to let Meryl Streep and Julia Roberts do this movie, you know, that Streep girl, you know, I think she's got a future and Roberts too by the way.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Tell me about this movie?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "It's a family drama about the - this movie is a comedy believe it or not.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "It's a family drama?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "It's good to see you old chap.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Wow, how are you?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "These are Christian Louboutin baby.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "What the hell are you wearing?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Now you're launching the HALO Awards?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "No, no honestly.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Is that supposed to be some sort of joke?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Come on man it stands for helping and leading others, it's a true positive thing that we do each and every year and this is the fifth year that we're doing it with Teen Nick and Nickelodeon.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "You a HALO?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Yes and we take celebrities and corporations and we shine that spotlight on, you know, teenagers and their community that are making the world a better place and we connect them all together.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Right, this is the real people, young people who have done something inspiring right?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Because I'm not happy with it right?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Yes it works.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "In my country in Britain we have free healthcare right?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Obviously it was brought in the National Health Center.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Was there ever a transitional period?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I'll say hey, haters are helping we don't argue with the help.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "At the moment, what would you say to him to try and galvanize things again for the last part of his tenure?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "I mean, that was unfortunate to me, I mean I felt like.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "How do you feel as such a hard working American when that happens?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Absolutely and especially when something could come to a stalemate like that I personally was disappointed in our system but that's not the first time I've been disappointed in our system.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Don't you feel sickened?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I could be called a lot worse things than that.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "How do you feel about being known, particularly by me as Mr. Mariah Carey?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Yes like a vulture.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "You're waiting for your opportunity?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "Not to take yourself too seriously and to actually enjoy each other, as much as you possibly can.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "What's the secret to a successful very high profile marriage?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I'm a hopeless romantic so I always thought I was in love until I found the real thing.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Had you ever been like properly in love before you met Mariah?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "If I said you could only be one thing for the rest of your life right?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "For the rest of my life, Stand Up Comedy.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "You can do TV like America's Got Talent or you can do Stand Up Comedy, which one would you do for the rest of your life?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "Absolutely that's where I started, hopefully that's where I'll finish and that's -- if you see, like obviously you showed a very clean clip of the special but to get on a stage.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "That's the real soul of Nick Cannon?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Because that's where everyone, like...", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Why is it called (inaudible) Nick Cannon?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "It's unapologetic.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Everyone says to you when they see?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "I think a little bit of both.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Which side are you leaning towards?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I don't think he was telling the truth.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "You think he lied?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Yeah, I mean that's harsh for me to say that because -- but it's you know, it's -- and I think that's where his real problem is going to be.", "docId": "131115pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "It's the same thing isn't it?", "qSentId": 611}]